Your argument is lacking
in all scientific merit.
It is well established
Superman cleans
his uniform
by flying into
Earth's yellow sun,
which incinerates any
contaminate matter
and leaves the
invulnerable
Kryptonian fabric unharmed
and daisy fresh.
What if he gets something
Kryptonian on it?
Like what?
I don't know.
Kryptonian mustard.
I think we can safely assume
that all Kryptonian condiments
were destroyed when the
planet Krypton exploded.
Or it turned into
mustard Kryptonite,
the only way to destroy
a rogue Kryptonian hotdog
threatening Earth.
LEONARD:
Raj, please,
let's stay serious here.
Superman's body
is Kryptonian,
therefore his sweat
is Kryptonian.
Yeah, what about
Kryptonian pit stains?
Superman doesn't
sweat on Earth.
WOLOWITZ:
Okay,
he's invited for dinner in
the Bottle City of Kandor.
He miniaturizes himself,
enters the city
where he loses his
superpowers. Now,
before dinner,
his host says,
"Who's up for a little
Kryptonian tetherball?"
Superman says "Sure,"
works up a sweat,
comes back to Earth,
his uniform now stained
with indestructible
Kryptonian perspiration.
Boo ya.
Superman would have
taken his uniform
to a Kandorian dry cleaner
before he left the Bottle.
"Kandorian dry cl..." I give up.
You can't have a rational
argument with this man.
WOLOWITZ:
Hey,
isn't that the guy who won
the MacArthur
genius grant last year?
No, not all at once.
Then how?
Leonard.
Now, Raj.
Now, Sheldon.
I didn't get a good look.
Can I go again?
No.
It's David
Underhill. So what?
SHELDON
So what?
His observation
of high-energy positrons
has provided the first
conclusive evidence
for the existence
of galactic dark matter.
I have two words for you.
The first is "big,"
the other's "whoop."
It is a big whoop.
It made almost all the work
you've done since you've been
here completely useless.
Did not.
Did, too.
Did...
Okay, maybe
some of it, but...
Look, the guy was just
in the right place,
at the right time with
the right paradigm-shifting
reinterpretation of the
universe. He got lucky.
In more ways than one.
He's a very handsome man.
Doesn't do anything for me.
If I was gonna go that way,
I'm more of a Zac
Ephron kinda guy.
Oh, yeah, like you have
a shot with Zac Ephron.
Excuse me...
Are you Leonard Hofstadter?
Uh... yeah.
I'm David Underhill.
Uh... y-yeah.
Yeah, Dr. Gablehauser
said if I wanted
to set something up
in the photomultiplier lab,
that you'd be able
to give me a hand?
You want to work with me?
Well,
if you have a little time, yeah.
Wow.... Y-yeah, sure.
Yeah, no problem. Uh...
Here's my home number.
Here's my cell.
Here's my office.
Here's my parents' number
up in New Jersey.
They always know how
to reach me. So...
Okay.
Congratulations on the MacArthur
Grant, by the way. Big fan.
Thanks. I'll call you.
Okay.
Bye-bye!
What are you looking at?
You've never seen
a hypocrite before?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
Trailing badly,
Wolowitz needs a strike
if he has any hopes of
catching up with Sheldon Cooper,
who is dominating
in the ninth frame
with a career-best 68.
LEONARD:
Hey, guys!
WOLOWITZ:
That doesn't count.
Do over! Do over!
There are no do-overs
in Wii bowling.
There are always do-overs
when my people play sports.
Where were you
that's more important
than Wii bowling night?
Actually, I was...
It's a rhetorical question.
There is nothing more important
than Wii bowling night.
Come on, it's just a video game.
And we suck at it.
(gasps)
Nice motivational speech
from the team captain.
Where were you?
I was working
with Dave Underhill.
Ooh, "Dave." Sounds like
Leonard's got a new BFF.
Actually, he's pretty cool.
I mean, not only is he
a brilliant scientist,
but it turns out he's
a Black Diamond skier.
He collects vintage motorcycles.
He plays in a rock band.
So? We're in
a rock band.
No...
We play Rock Band on our X-Box.
Nice motivational speech
from our lead guitarist.
He's funny, too.
He does this
hysterical impersonation
of Stephen Hawking
having phone sex.
(laughing)
(imitating):
What are you wearing?
That's not...
He does it better.
Anyway, he said he was gonna
take me to the gym tomorrow,
so I'm gonna go
practice my situps.
Whoa. Humongous man crush, dude.
Yeah. It's officially
a bro-mance.
Hey, Sheldon,
are you and Leonard
putting up a Christmas tree?
No, because we don't celebrate
the ancient pagan festival
of Saturnalia.
Saturnalia?
Gather round, kids,
it's time for Sheldon's
beloved Christmas special.
In the pre-Christian era,
as the winter solstice
approached and the plants died,
pagans brought evergreen boughs
into their homes
as an act of sympathetic
magic, intended
to guard the life essences
of the plants until spring.
This custom was
later appropriated
by Northern Europeans
and eventually it becomes
the so-called Christmas tree.
And that, Charlie Brown, is
what boredom is all about.
Okay, well,
thank you
for that, but I got
you and Leonard
a few silly neighbor gifts,
so I'll just
put them under my tree.
Wait!
You bought me a present?
Uh-huh.
Why would you do such a thing?
I don't know.
'Cause it's Christmas?
Oh, Penny. I know you think
you're being generous,
but the foundation
of gift-giving is reciprocity.
You haven't given me a gift.
You've given me an obligation.
Don't feel bad, Penny, it's
a classic rookie mistake.
My first Hanukah
with Sheldon,
he yelled at me
for eight nights.
Now, hey, it's okay.
You don't have to get
me anything in return.
Of course I do.
The essence of the custom
is that I now have to go out
and purchase for you
a gift of commensurate value
and representing the same
perceived level of friendship
as that represented
by the gift you've given me.
It's no wonder suicide rates
skyrocket this time of year.
Okay, you know what? Forget it.
I'm not giving you a present.
No, it's too late. I see it.
That elf sticker
says, "To Sheldon."
The die has been cast.
The moving finger has writ
Hannibal has crossed the alps.
(whispering)
(laughing)
I know. It's funny
when it's not
happening to us.
Sheldon, I am very, very sorry.
No. No, I brought this on myself
by being such an endearing
and important part of your life.
I'm going to need
a ride to the mall.
It's happening to us.
(thud)
Ow!
Ha-ha-ha. Ow.
Are you gonna make it?
Yeah, I guess.
All right.
Thanks for letting me
try out your motorcycle.
No problem.
I had no idea
it was so heavy.
The thing just fell right
over on me, didn't it?
Yeah. Lucky for you
it wasn't moving.
Oh, hey, Leonard.
Ooh, are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
It's just a little
motorcycle accident.
My God, how fast were you going?
I don't know. It's
all such a blur.
(laughing)
Good one. He couldn't
even get it started.
(laughing)
Hi. Dave.
Hi.
Penny. So it's your motorcycle?
Uh-huh.
Ohh...
Is it okay?
It's fine.
Lucky for the bike
it landed on my leg.
You mind giving me a hand
with speed racer here?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
So, um, Dave, how
do you know Leonard?
I'm a physicist.
(laughing)
No, you're not.
Why is that
so surprising?
Uh, well, it's just that
the physicists I know
are indoorsy and pale.
I'm not indoorsy.
I just wear
the appropriate sun block
because I don't take
melanoma lightly.
So, are you
and Leonard working on
an experiment together?
Yeah,
actually we are.
Yeah, we're examining
the radiation levels
of photomultiplier tubes
for a new
dark matter detector.
Uh, sweetie, sweetie,
Dave was talking.
You know, I love science.
Since when?
Since always.
Call me a geek,
but I am just nuts
for the whole subatomic-
particle thing.
The last thing I would
ever call you is a geek.
(laughs) Ha. Well,
that's what I am--
queen of the nerds.
DAVE:
Well, if you like,
I could show you the
lab we're working in.
We've got some cool toys,
you know-- lasers and stuff.
You know, I have always wanted
to see a big science lab.
Since when?
Since always.
Leonard, are you
okay here?
Uh...
Yeah. I guess.
How 'bout we go
see it now?
Maybe afterwards we take
the bike up the coast,
We grab a little
bite to eat...
Um... Yeah. Yeah,
that sounds great.
Let me just
get my jacket.
(door closes)
Boy, she'll do, huh?
Yeah, if you
like that type.
So, you and her...?
No, just neighbors.
Really.
I don't know how you live
next door to that
without doing
something about it.
Actually...
science is my lady.
Okay. Let's go.
All right.
See you tomorrow,
Leonard.
See ya. 'Bye, Penny.
Have fun.
(thuds against door)
Yes?
Did you forget your key?
(Christmas music playing)
I don't see anything
in here a woman would want.
You're kidding.
You've got lotions
and bath oils and soaps.
I mean, that's the
estrogen hat trick.
What it is
is a cacophonous assault
of eucalyptus, bayberry,
cinnamon and vanilla.
It's as if my head were trapped
in the pajamas of a sultan.
Sheldon, if you don't
like this stuff,
let's just go next door
and build her a bear.
I told you before,
bears are terrifying.
WOLOWITZ:
Come on,
bath stuff.
It's perfect!
You got a scented candle,
a cleansing buff,
spearmint and green tea scented
bath oil, promotes relaxation.
That presupposes
Penny is tense.
She knows you.
She's tense.
We all are.
Buy a basket!
Excuse me, we're ready.
No, we're not.
Let's say for a moment
that I accept
the bath item gift hypothesis,
I now lay the following
conundrum at your feet:
Which size?
This one.
Let's go.
You put no thought into that.
I'm sorry.
Uh... this one.
Let's go!
I have insufficient
data to proceed.
Excuse me, miss?
Yes?
If I were to give you
this gift basket,
based on that action alone
and no other data,
infer and describe
the hypothetical relationship
that exists between us.
Excuse me?
Here.
Now, are we friends?
Colleagues? Lovers?
Are you my grandmother?
I don't understand what
you're talking about
and you're making me
a little uncomfortable.
See? Sounds just
like you and Penny.
We'll take it.
(laughing)
Hey, Leonard.
Come, join us.
Oh, hey, Dave.
And Penny, what a surprise.
Hey, Leonard.
Dave was just showing me
around the university.
You know,
this place
is unbelievable!
Yeah, I know.
I've been offering
to show you around
for a year and a half.
You always said you had yoga.
I never said that.
Maybe I heard you wrong.
A lot of words
sound like "yoga."
This is an amazing
woman, Leonard.
She has a curious
and agile mind,
not to mention being curious
and agile in other respects.
(laughing):
Oh, shut up!
Yes, please shut up.
So, um, Dave,
don't you think you and I
should get back to the lab?
You know, that dark matter
isn't going to detect itself.
Actually, I was thinking about
taking the afternoon off
so I could work on another
experiment with Penny.
Really? We're going
to do an experiment?
Uh-huh. We're going to explore
the effects of tequila shots
on a gorgeous
22-year-old woman.
It's not an experiment!
You saw what happened
last night. (laughing)
You ready to go?
Yeah.
Oh, can I drive
the motorcycle?
Yeah, why not?
You can't do any
worse than Leonard.
That's funny.
By the way, my leg
is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
Mmm, great news, Leonard.
I've solved my
Penny gift dilemma.
Yippee.
You see, the danger was that I
might under or over-reciprocate,
but I have devised
a foolproof plan.
See, I will open
her gift to me first
and then excuse myself,
feigning digestive distress.
Then I'll look up the
price of her gift online,
choose the basket
closest to that value,
give it to her
and then I'll return the
others for a full refund.
Brilliant.
It is, isn't it?
Is it okay if I hide
them in your room?
The smell makes
me nauseated.
Do whatever you want.
Thank you, that's very gracious.
Gentlemen.
Why couldn't you have just
done what Leonard did
and get Penny
a new boyfriend?
My leg is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
(knocking on door)
Okay, I have just
one question for you.
While I am perfectly happy with
the way things are between us,
you said that
you didn't want
to go out with me because
I was too smart for you!
Well, news flash, lady:
David Underhill is ten
times smarter than me!
You'd have to drive a
railroad spike into his brain
for me to beat him at checkers!
Next to him,
I'm like one of those
sign-language gorillas
who knows how to ask for grapes!
So, my question is...
What's up with that?!
(crying):
Why are you yelling at me?
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Never mind, we're cool.
Dave is not smarter than you.
He's an idiot.
Really? Why would you say that?
Because a smart guy takes
the nude photos of his wife
off his cell phone before
he tries to take nude photos
of his girlfriend.
He tried to take
nude photos of you?
That's what you took
from that?!
The guy is married!
Oh, yeah.
I'm so-- Oh, that's terrible.
And you, if you are so okay
with the way things
are between us,
why are you so jealous?
Well, uh...
The important thing is he's
married and that's terrible!
Nice save, genius.
Eggnog?
Lactose.
It's just rum.
It stopped being eggnog
like half an hour ago.
Smooth.
Smoother than you.
Come on, it's Christmas,
just give me this one.
Okay, Merry Christmas.
By the way, my leg
is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
(knocking on door)
Merry Christmas.
How's your leg?
Very good, thanks
for asking. Come on in.
Ah, good, Penny, you're
here to exchange gifts.
You'll be pleased to know
I'm prepared for
whatever you have to offer.
Okay, here.
I should note I'm having
some digestive distress,
so, if I excuse myself
abruptly, don't be alarmed.
Oh, a napkin.
Turn it over.
"To Sheldon,
"live long and prosper.
Leonard Nimoy."
Yeah, he came
into the restaurant.
Sorry the napkin's dirty.
He wiped his mouth with it.
I possess the DNA
of Leonard Nimoy?!
Well...
Yeah, yeah. I guess.
But look, he signed it.
Do you realize
what this means?!
All I need is a healthy ovum
and I can grow
my own Leonard Nimoy!
Okay, all I'm giving you
is the napkin, Sheldon.
Be right back.
Here. Open it.
Oh, a gift certificate
for motorcycle lessons.
Very thoughtful.
Yeah, and I checked.
Not letting the
bike fall on you
while standing still
is lesson one.
Oh, then, I think you'll
appreciate what I got you.
Okay.
"101 Totally Cool Science
Experiments for Kids."
You know, 'cause you're
so into science.
Sheldon!
What did you do?!
I know!
It's not enough, is it?
Here.
Leonard, look!
Sheldon's hugging me.
It's a Saturnalia miracle.